Guide to the Charles E. Palm papers,1956-1986.
Palm, Charles E. papers,1956-1986.
  - Budget Requests, 1961-62. McKeegan, Paul L., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - College of Agriculture Budget, 1959-60., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Biometrics. New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Plant Breeding., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Botany. Banks, Harlan P.; Steward, F.C.; Kennedy, W. Keith; Boynton, Damon; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Botany., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - College of Agriculture Council, Spring Meeting. Adams, Morton; Wickham, John; New York State College of Agriculture, Advisory Council., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - College of Agriculture, Other Colleges and Long-Range Planning Committee. Kennedy, W. Keith., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - College Tomato Committee., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Conservation. Swanson, Gustav A.; Atwood, Sanford S.; Hamilton, Lawrence S.; Bond, Maurice C.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Conservation; New York State, Dept, of Conservation; New York State Fish and Wildlife Management Board; Arnot Forest; Youth correction camps., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Commencement Procedures., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Contract Groups., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Cornell Council. Price, Robert D.; Cornell University, Council., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Cornell University Council., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Councils and Boards, C.E. Palm. Meigs, Robert B., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Countryman. Razinsky, Edward L., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Day. Krause, Harvey., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Students Activities and Scheduling., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Dairy Industry. Holland, Robert F.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Dairy Industry., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Economics Letters. Kiplinger Letters; Washington Situation; Lowdown on Farm Affairs., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - School of Education. Stutz, Frederick H.; Colman, Gould P.; Gibson, Anson W.; Bail, Joe P.; Cornell University, School of Education; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Rural Education; Ford Foundation., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Educational Policy Committee., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Entomology. Schwardt, Herbert H.; Pimentel, David; Franclemont, John G.; Gyrisco, George G.; Sevin; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Entomology; Gypsy Moth; Pesticides; Quarantines., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - National Science Foundation Cabinet Project. New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Entomology; National Science Foundation., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Estimates., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Experiment Station., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Experiment Stations Legislation Program. American Assn. of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Cornell Experiment Station. Kennedy, W. Keith; Cornell University, Agricultural Experiment Station;; National Science Foundation., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Cornell Experiment Station. Kennedy, W. Keith; Gibson, Anson W.; Cornell University, Agricultural Experiment Station; National Science Foundation; International Grassland Conference; Phosdrin., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Applications, Ithaca. New York State Agricultural Experiment Station; New York State College of Agriculture Office of Resident Instruction., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Geneva Agricultural Experiment Station. Heinicke, Arthur J.; McEwen, Freeman L.; Peterson, Arthur H.; Hand, David B.; New York State Horticultural Society; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Pomology., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Geneva News Releases. New York State Agricultural Experiment Station., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Applications, Geneva. Adams, Morton; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Extension Service. Bond, Maurice C.; Durfee, Arthur E.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service; Grange League Federation., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Extension Service. Bond, Maurice C.; Durfee, Arthur E.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service; Rural Civil Defense Program., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Extension Service Policy Statement. Bond, Maurice C.; Smith, Herbert H.; Durfee, Arthur E.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Entomology, Extension. New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Extension Teaching and Information. Knapp, James S.; Morse, Roger A.; Ames, Robert J.; Ward, William B.; Turner, Richard G.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service; Cornell University, Committee on Publications; Gypsy Moth., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Extension Service, Policies. New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Extension Organization. Bond, Maurice C; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Madison County 4-H. Pease, Wilbur F.; Coffin, Mrs. William; New York State Cooperative Extension Service, 4-H; New York State, Office of the Attorney General., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - State Agricultural Leaders. New York State Cooperative Extension Service; New York State Fish and Wildlife Management Board., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Extension Dispute. Lefkowitz, Louis J.; Bond, Maurice C.; Pease, Wilbur F.; Coffin, Mrs. William; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Extension Central Advisory Committee. Quigley, Robert M.; Bond, Maurice C., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Wildlife Extension Project. New York State Fish and Wildlife Management Board., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Isaac DeHollander Onion Claim. DeHollander, Isaac; Muka, Arthur A.; Kennedy, W. Keith; Insecticides., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Insect and Disease Report, Cooperative Extension., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Farm Problem, "What Are The Choices?" Bond, Maurice C.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Extension, County Agricultural Agents. Nice, Glenn D.; Cramer, R.W.; Huth, Joseph E.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - State 4-H Leaders. Pease, Wilbur F., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Comparative Extension Education Program. Hearne, Cannon C.; Kelsey, Lincoln D., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Cornell University, University Faculty. Hanson, C. Arnold; Religious holidays., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Courtesy Faculty Appointments. Hanson, C. Arnold; Brady, Nyle C.; Gibson, Anson W., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Agricultural Faculty Budget Adjustments., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Food Science and Technology Building, Dedication Plans. Heinicke, Arthur J.; Dalrymple, Daniel M.; Rockefeller, Nelson A.; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station; Food processing; Food Research Program., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Farm and Home Week. New York State College of Home Economics., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Farm and Home Week. Rozelle, Richard J.; New York State College of Home Economics; New York State College of Agriculture; Farm and Home Week., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Other University Trips and Notes., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Claim, E.J. Chapman, Orchard Fire. Barton, Donald W., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - New York State College of Agriculture, Faculty., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Farm and Home Week Committee., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Farm and Home Week 1960. Butz, Earl L.; Farm and Home Week., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - College Fleet. Murphy, John C., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture. Seeley, John G.; Langhans, Robert W.; New York State Turfgrass Association; New York State Flower Growers, Inc.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Floriculture Research Project 1959. Seeley, John G.; New York State Nurserymen's Association., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Correspondence. Brown, Lindsey A.; Sherlock, Philip M., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Students. Williams, David B.; Cornell University, Foreign Student Office., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Visitors. Bond, Maurice C., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Visitors Program. Hanks, Elton K., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Freshman Orientation Program., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - CM. Nevin Presentation, 3 June 1960. Nevin, Charles M.; Cornell University, Dept, of Geology., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Gibson Dinner. Gibson, Anson W., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Gibson, Anson W., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Graduate School. Boynton, Damon; Kennedy, W. Keith; McConnell, John W.; Cornell University, Graduate School., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Growth Chamber. Kennedy, W. Keith; Growth chambers; Greenhouses., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Hatch Amended Assignments. Kennedy, W. Keith; Hatch funds., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Hedlund, "What's Ahead for N.E. Agriculture." Hedlund, Glenn W., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Heinicke Luncheon. Heinicke, Arthur J., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Home Economics. Canoyer, Helen G.; Personius, Catherine J.; New York State College of Home Economics., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - New York State College of Home Economics, Council. Canoyer, Helen G.; Wood, Mary B.; New York State College of Home Economics Council., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - New York State College of Agriculture, Ho-Nun-De-Kah Barbeque., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Ho-Nun-De-Kah. Marr, John; Hertel, John P., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - School of Hotel Administration. Meek, Howard B.; Cornell University, School of Hotel Administration., 1959-60 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Human Development, Human Relations Program. Dildine, Glenn C.; Bond, Maurice C., 1959-60 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - School of Industrial and Labor Relations. McConnell, John W.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1959-60 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Cornell University Industry Park. Cornell University Industry Research Park., 1959-60 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Irrigation Project 1959., 1959-60 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Library. Forman, Ruth E.; Powell, Whiton; Devereux, Edward C., 1959-60 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Unification of University Libraries., 1959-60 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Los Banos, Philippine Staff. Umali, D.L.; Uichanco, Leopoldo B.; Univ. of the Philippines; New York State College of Agriculture, Los Banos Project., 1959-60 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Los Banos, Cornell Members. Knapp, Halsey B.; Somers, G. Fred; Von Oppenfeld, Horst; Univ. of the Philippines., 1959-60 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Los Banos Final Report. Univ. of the Philippines; New York State College of Agriculture, Los Banos Project., 1952-1960 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Mail Volume, College of Agriculture. Foster, Charles H., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Mann Library. Gibson, Anson W., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Dr. W.I. Myers. Myers, William I.; Barton, Donald W.; Van Wagenen, Jared; New York Farm Electrification Council., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Dean Myers Retirement Banquet. Myers, William I., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Cornell University News Bureau., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - NEW # 22, Regional Research Project., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - N.E. Project # 23. Jensen, Neal F., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - N.E. Project # 36, Frear, Starnes, Gyrisco., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Nominations Committee., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - School of Nutrition. Barnes, Richard H.; Cornell University, Graduate School of Nutrition., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Personnel Policy, Cornell University, Non-Academic. Cornell University, Personnel Office., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Plant Breeding. Murphy, Royse P.; Srb, Adrian M.; Johnson, Alvin A.; Everett, Herbert L.; Wallace, Bruce; Demerec, Milislav; Plaisted, Robert L.; Myers, William I.; Oak Ridge Institute of Nuclear Studies; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Plant Breeding., 1957-1960 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Symposium "Mutation and Plant Breeding" 28 Nov - 2 Dec 1960. New York State College of Agriculture, Dept of Plant Breeding., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Seed Storage Building, Plant Breeding. Murphy, Royce P.; Billings, Russell R.; Stanford Seed Company; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Plant Breeding., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Plant Pathology. Kent, George C.; Massey, Louis M.; National Science Foundation, Undergraduate Research Program; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Plant Pathology; Golden Nematode., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Plant Physiology. Steward, F.C.; Banks, Harlan P.; Rockefeller Foundation; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Botany., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Policy and Procedures for Handling Grants., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Pomology. Hoffman, Melvin B.; Smock, Robert M.; Greene, Laurenz; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Pomology; International Cooperation Administration; Inst. Sperimentale Di Fruitcoltura Laboratoire Du Phytotron; Fruit industry; Pesticides., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Poultry Housing. Baker, Robert C.; Bruckner, Jacob H.; Ostrander, Charles E.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Poultry Industry., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Poultry Husbandry. Bruckner, Jacob H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Poultry Husbandry., 1953-1960 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Practice Requirement, Administration of Requirements., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Publications Committee., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Radiological Safety Committee., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Cornell University Research Club., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Resident Instruction. Harden, Leigh H.; Hertel, John P.; Gibson, Anson W.; Tyler, Howard S.; Stutz, Frederick H.; Javits, Jacob K.; Catherwood, Martin P.; New York State College of Agriculture Office of Resident Instruction; European Productivity Agency; Alpha Zeta; National Science Foundation., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Graduate Program. Ridgeway, Richard; Gyrisco, George G., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Romanoff, Alexis L., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Rural Education Proposal for Transfer to School of Education. Stutz, Frederick H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Rural Education., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Rural School Leaflet. Cornell Science Leaflets., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Rural Sociology. Larson, Olaf F.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Rural Sociology; Migrant labor., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Safety Division. Herson, James M., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Salaries, College of Agriculture., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Salary Distribution vs. Earned Degrees., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Scheduling Public Events. Cornell University, Office of Student Activities., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Cornell Science Leaflet., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Agricultural Scholarships. Bruska, Walter G., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Scientific Meeting Travel Policy., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - College Seed Committee., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Sloan Distinguished Professors. Alfred P. Sloan Foundation., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Social Science Research Center., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Reasons for Soil Conservation Committee Remaining in College of Agriculture., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Student Applications., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Committee on University Standards, Student Government., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Student-Faculty Relationships. Razinsky, Edward L., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Student Organizations. Summerskill, John; University Faculty Committee on Student Affairs., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Student Correspondence. Abrahams, Peter D., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Student Organization Officials, Dean, Directors and Dept. Heads Luncheon., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Prospective Students., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Student Activities Calendar, Spring 1960., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Summer Session. Smith, William A., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - State University Unit Heads Meeting. SUNY., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Tax Policies. Meigs, Robert B., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Travel Allowances. Cornell University, Finance and Business Office., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Traveling Fellowships. Swanson, Gustav A.; Semel, Maurice., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Applications for Traveling Award, 1960. Smith, Edward H., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Waiver Tuition., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Replies to Letter re Tuition Exchange Plan. Williams, Herbert H., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Vegetable Crops. Munger, Henry M.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Vegetable Crops., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Vegetable Advisory Committee., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - New York State Veterinary College. Poppensiek, George C., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Water Resources Planning. New York State College of Agriculture, Water Resources Center., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Water Resources Planning. Van Lare, Frank E.; New York State College of Agriculture, Water Resources Center; United States Dept, of Agriculture, Soil Conservation Service., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Water Resources Planning. Van Lare, Frank E.; Wilm, Harold G.; Christensen, N.A.; New York State College of Agriculture, Water Resources Center; New York State, Dept, of Conservation., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - A Miscellaneous. Anderson, William A.; Alexander, Charles P.; Allied Chemical Corporation; American Association for the Advancement of Science., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Morton Adams. Adams, Morton; Brunk, Max E., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Agricultural Chemicals. Dorland, Wayne E., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Agricultural and Technical Institutes. Wheeler, Ray L.; Foote, Norman H.; SUNY Agricultural and Technical Institute, Cobleskill., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Agricultural Conservation Program, New York., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Alpha Zeta., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - American Agriculturist Foundation. Eastman, Edward R.; Ingalls, Irving W.; Cosline, Hugh L.; American Agriculturist; American Agriculturist Foundation., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - American Council on Education., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Animal Agriculture Conference, Purdue, 1960. National Institute of Animal Agriculture., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Atomic Fallout re Protection of Livestock for Breeding Purposes. Atomic fallout., 1960 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - B Miscellaneous. Butz, Earl L.; Beneway, Frank W., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Broccoli and Cauliflower Residue Survey. Muka, Arthur A., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - C Miscellaneous. Catherwood, Martin P., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - California Growers Council. Council of California Growers., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Chemagro Corporation. Von Rumker, Rosmarie., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Clippings., 1960 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - College-Federal Agency Council., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Continental Can Company., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Co-ops., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Council on Rural Education., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Dairy Farming, Costs Index. Grange League Federation., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Dairymen's League Affiliation Program. Bond, Maurice C.; Hamrick, Lee; Dairymen's League Cooperative Association., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Dairymen's League Cooperative Association. Willers, Diedrich K.; Benham, Stanley H.; Dairymen's League Cooperative Association., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - E Miscellaneous. Stutz, Frederick H.; Evans, H.J.; Pesticides., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Eastman Stage., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Economic Intelligence., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Economic Outlook. Agricultural Situation and Outlook., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Presidential Dinner, May 1960, Eisenhower Dinner. Eisenhower, Dwight D.; Committee for International Economic Growth. (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - 11th International Congress of Entomology, Vienna 1960. Internationaler Entomologenkongress. (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Entomological Societies. Woodbury, E.N.; Entomological Society of America; National Science Board., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - European Productivity Agency. Hanks, Elton K., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - F Miscellaneous. Kimball, Keith H.; Fallon, Edmund H.; Grange League Federation; Finger Lakes Wine Growers Association., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Farm Club of New York-Phillips, E.H., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Farm Electrification Council. New York Farm Electrification Council; Niagara Mohawk Power Corporation; Rural electrification., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Farm Problem. Stockpiles., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Federal Land Banks, Farm Conditions in Northeast. Farm Credit Banks of Springfield., 1960 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Focus on Food Markets. New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Foreign Agriculture. Keating, Kenneth B.; Hearne, Cannon C., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - New York State College of Forestry., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Food Machinery and Chemical Corporation., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - G Miscellaneous. Goodrich, John G.; Hairanan, Robert E.; Geigy Agricultural Chemicals; Grange League Federation., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - General Foods Corporation, Birds Eye. Pesticides., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Grange League Federation. Gervan, R. Bruce; Ranney, Warren A., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Grange League Federation Administrators Conference., 1960 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Grange League Federation Public Relations., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Grange League Federation Week. Ranney, Warren A., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Golden Nematode., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Governor's Office. Rockefeller, Nelson A.; Root, Oren., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - H Miscellaneous. Rumler, Robert H.; Hardison, Lewis M.; Helmerking, Wilhelm; Holstein-Friesian Association of America., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - High School Natural Science Program. Morse, Roger A., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Hotels., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - I Miscellaneous. National College of Agriculture in South Vietnam., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - New York State International Farm Youth Exchange., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Instructional Procedures., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Insurance., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - International Cooperation Administration., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Ithaca Chamber of Commerce Agricultural Committee., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - J Miscellaneous. Johnson, Marion I.; Jones, E. Parry., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - K Miscellaneous. Kleberg, Richard M., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - L Miscellaneous. Leagans, J. Paul; Lefkowitz, Louis J., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - American Assn. of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities. Gibson, Anson W., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - M Miscellaneous. McAllister, Mary H.; Myers, Rowland M.; Morse Chain Company., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Metropolitan Cooperative Milk Producers Bargaining Agency. Forsythe, Robert C.; Dairy industry., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 65)